module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'When was Firefox created (for beta)?', 
      a: '1998', 
      b: '2000',
      c: '2002',
      d: '2004',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'What was the original name for Firefox?', 
      a: 'Firepoint', 
      b: 'Mozilla Sun',
      c: 'Firewatch',
      d: 'Phoenix',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'According to latest estimates, what percentage of the internet uses Firefox (across all devices)?', 
      a: '<5%', 
      b: '5% - 10%',
      c: '10% - 15%',
      d: '15% - 20%',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'What percentage of the internet users Firefox as a desktop browser?', 
      a: '<5%', 
      b: '5% - 10%',
      c: '10% - 15%',
      d: '15% - 20%',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Mozilla was created by employees from which company?', 
      a: 'Yahoo', 
      b: 'MSN',
      c: 'Miscrosoft',
      d: 'Netscape',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'Where did Firefox allegedly get its name from?', 
      a: 'A developer\'s pet corgi', 
      b: 'A nickname for red pandas',
      c: 'A defunct dijon mustard',
      d: 'An overheating computer',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Mozilla\'s logo rebranded in 2017 to replace its logotype Ls with what?', 
      a: 'exclamation points', 
      b: 'ones',
      c: 'slashes',
      d: 'colons',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'Firefox is also a 1982 movie (with a 38% RT score) directed by who?', 
      a: 'Clint Eastwood', 
      b: 'Rob Reiner',
      c: 'Tony Scott',
      d: 'Luc Besson',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'The Mozilla Corporation is actuallyâ€¦', 
      a: 'a subsidiary of Google', 
      b: 'less than 100 people',
      c: 'a not-for-profit',
      d: 'partially owned by Will Ferrell',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'In the past five years, which is the only other major browser to increase its usage share (after Chrome)?', 
      a: 'Firefox', 
      b: 'Safari',
      c: 'Edge',
      d: 'None of them.',
      answer: 'b'
    }
  ]
};
